Guide to the Associate University Librarian for Collection Development, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Ann S. Okerson as associate university librarian for collection development, circa 1990-1995, Accession 2004-A-099
  - Cataloging 97/98, 1996 December 19 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - CDC, 1999 June 15 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Center for Research Libraries, 1992-1999 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Cervantes, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Chadwyck-Healey, 1999 October 1 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Eichenberg, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Gore-Browne Sir Stewart Paper, 1984-1992 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Signature: RFW, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Tufts, 1971-1988 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - BNA (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - CJK recon (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Classics (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Classics (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Codger (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Codger Documents (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Collection development (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Commission on preservation and access (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Computer guidelines/manuals (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Confu (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - 1996 Confu (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - 1995 Confu (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Consultants (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Copyright (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Council on Library resources (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Council on Library resources (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - CRL (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Databases (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Development, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Development, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Dewg (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Digital Library (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Digital Library Federation (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Digital Library2 grant (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Distance Learning (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Divinity (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Divinity, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Divinity, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Divinity documents (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Divinity Library (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Donations (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - DVD Digital video disk (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Human Resources (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - IBM Proposal (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - EAC Annual report, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - East Asian collection FY 97-1998 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - East Asian collection FY 96-1997 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - East Asian collection (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - EIU (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Electronic Publications (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Electronic Publications Collection Specialist (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Electronic Recourses (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Elsevier (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Elsevier (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Endowments (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Esposito (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Forestry Library (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Forestry Library (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Getty Proposal (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Gifts correspondence (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Gordon and Breach (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Grants and Contracts (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Greek/Turkish, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Greek/Turkish, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Greek/Turkish, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Harper's Weekly (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Harrassowitz (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Henkel (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Historical Sound Recordings (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - La Clair (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Recs/Resumes (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Withdrawal/Discard Policy (Paul Conway's File) (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Andrew's study, 1985-1989 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Foreign travel, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Graduate Club membership, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - ICPSR (Inter- University Consortium for Political and social research), 1984- 1987 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - IFLA, 1995-1999 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - ILL Cooperative Agreements, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Informed Strategies, 1998 August 19 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - International Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Invoices, 1995 December 18 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - IPEDS, 1998 August (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - ITS, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Journal Pricing (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Journal Series (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Judaica (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Judaica (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Judaica, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Judaica, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Judaica, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Latin American (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Latin American, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Latin American, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Latin American Collection (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Letter of Agreement (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - LBO (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - LIB Licenses (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Library Management Team (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Library Policy (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Library Shelving Facility (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Library Shelving Facility (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Library Space Planning (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - LIB Systems steering (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Loughborough University (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Luna/Amico (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Management Team (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Management Team (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Manuscripts and Archives (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Maps, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Maps, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Maps/Travel (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Math Library (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Maps Collection, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - MDAS (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - Medical Library (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Medical Library (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Medline (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - Mellon Foundation (Box 5, Folder 196)
  - Membership (Box 5, Folder 197)
  - Memo MSSA (Box 5, Folder 198)
  - Memo Music Library (Box 5, Folder 199)
  - Misc (Box 5, Folder 200)
  - MOA (Box 5, Folder 201)
  - Model license (Box 5, Folder 202)
  - MSSA (Box 5, Folder 203)
  - Music, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 204)
  - Music, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 205)
  - Music Library (Box 5, Folder 206)
  - Music Library (Box 5, Folder 207)
  - Nanette Stahl's AJL 98 Paper (Box 5, Folder 208)
  - NATC (Box 5, Folder 209)
  - National Science Foundation (Box 5, Folder 210)
  - NELINET (Box 5, Folder 211)
  - Near East (Box 5, Folder 212)
  - Near East (Box 5, Folder 213)
  - Near East, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 214)
  - Near East, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 215)
  - NFAIS (Box 5, Folder 216)
  - Nota Bene (Box 5, Folder 217)
  - Periodicals Project (Box 5, Folder 218)
  - SB Directories (Box 5, Folder 219)
  - Selection (Box 5, Folder 220)
  - Annual Reports, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Blackwells (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Books for Bosnia Project (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Faxon and Elsevier (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Harrossowitz (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Stanford University Advisory committee (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - NDLF (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - NDLTD project (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - NPAC (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - Occasional Papers (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - ODLC (Box 6, Folder 232)
  - Ohio State (Box 6, Folder 233)
  - Oracle (Box 6, Folder 234)
  - Orbis (Box 6, Folder 235)
  - OUP (Box 6, Folder 236)
  - Personnel- job Descriptions (Box 6, Folder 238)
  - Pierson Fellow (Box 6, Folder 239)
  - Poole's (Box 6, Folder 240)
  - Preservation (Box 6, Folder 242)
  - Rand (Box 6, Folder 243)
  - RECBIR (Box 6, Folder 244)
  - RLIN (Box 6, Folder 245)
  - Roth (Box 6, Folder 247)
  - RSC (Box 6, Folder 248 - 249)
  - RSC, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 250)
  - RSC, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 251)
  - RSC, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 252)
  - Science Libraries (Box 6, Folder 253)
  - Science Park (Box 6, Folder 254)
  - Science Patent Depositories (Box 6, Folder 255)
  - Sciences, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 256)
  - Sciences, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 257)
  - SEA, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 258)
  - SEA, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 259)
  - Slavic (Box 6, Folder 260)
  - Slavic and E. European (Box 6, Folder 261)
  - Slavic, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 262)
  - Slavic, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 263)
  - Slavic, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 264)
  - Social Sciences Library (Box 6, Folder 266)
  - South East Asia (Box 6, Folder 267)
  - South West Asia (Box 6, Folder 268)
  - SSLIS (Box 6, Folder 269)
  - SSLIS, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 270)
  - SSLIS, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 271)
  - SSLIS, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 272)
  - STM (Box 6, Folder 273)
  - Systems (Box 6, Folder 274)
  - Thank you (Box 6, Folder 275)
  - Thomason Science (Box 6, Folder 276)
  - Title VI (Box 6, Folder 277)
  - UCCIT, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 278)
  - UCCIT (Box 6, Folder 279)
  - UIAS (Box 6, Folder 280)
  - Unions (Box 6, Folder 281)
  - Video conferencing (Box 6, Folder 282)
  - WWW (Box 6, Folder 283)
  - Yale Alumni (Box 6, Folder 284)
  - Yale Information (Box 6, Folder 285)
  - Yale Policies (Box 6, Folder 286)
  - Yale Publications Working Group (Box 6, Folder 287)
  - Yale University: Tax exempt permit (Box 6, Folder 288)
  - Yankee (Box 6, Folder 289)
  - YCIAS (Box 6, Folder 290)
  - Book budget requests, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 291)
  - Copyright Clearance payments (Box 7, Folder 292)
  - Discard program (Box 7, Folder 293)
  - Action Planning, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 294)
  - American Physical Society (Box 7, Folder 295)
  - BIOSIS, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 296)
  - MAKS paper, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 297)
  - CRL (Box 7, Folder 298)
  - CRL- general (Box 7, Folder 299)
  - CRL- purchase proposal (Box 7, Folder 300)
  - Chadwick Healy (Box 7, Folder 301)
  - Chadwick Healy Electronic Access (Box 7, Folder 302)
  - CDC, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 303)
  - CDC off campus shelving (Box 7, Folder 304)
  - Other conferences (Box 7, Folder 305)
  - Reprint contract (Box 7, Folder 306)
  - Moorhead (Box 7, Folder 307)
  - Princeton/Mich Doc service (Box 7, Folder 308)
  - SEIRM (Box 7, Folder 309)
  - Copyright policies (Box 7, Folder 310)
  - University of Michigan (Box 7, Folder 311)
  - "We" Lindbergh Republican/Dover (Box 7, Folder 312)
  - IITF (Box 7, Folder 313)
  - Legal Papers (Box 7, Folder 314)
  - Fair use (Box 7, Folder 315)
  - Computer copyright and usage dilemma (Box 7, Folder 316)
  - Documents/ MISC (Box 7, Folder 317)
  - Copyright/ MISC (Box 7, Folder 318)
  - Brown and Lehman (Box 7, Folder 319)
  - Disturbed Patrons (Box 7, Folder 320)
  - Divinity School, 1991-1996 (Box 7, Folder 321)
  - Divinity School, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 322)
  - Dutch Books at YUL, 1980-1989 (Box 7, Folder 323)
- Associate University Librarian for Collection Development records, 1954-2011; Accession 2012-A-059
  Restricted until January 1, 2046
  - Records of Ann S. Okerson as associate university librarian for collection development
    - Appalachian College Association (ACA), 2005-2008 (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
    - American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS) Commission on Cyberinfrastructure for the Humanities and Social Sciences, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Association for Computing Machinery (ACM), 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
    - Acquisitions, 2006-2008 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - American Library Association (ALA), 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - American Library Association - Library Networks Cooperatives and Consortia (ALA-LNCC), 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Alexander Street Press, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Association of Learned and Professional Society Publishers (ALPSP), 2008 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Alumni, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Amazon, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Association of Research Libraries (ARL) Budget Survey, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Association of Research Libraries (ARL) Correspondence, 1997-2008 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Association of Research Libraries (ARL) Statistics, 1995-2008 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Artemis, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - ARTstor, 2004-2009 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - AUP - Report on the 2006-2007 FAS Faculty Survey, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - BiblioVault, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Bioline International, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - BioOne, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - BioMed Central, 2004-2009 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Blackwell Seminar, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Borrow Direct - Notes and E-Mails, 2002-2011 (Box 1, Folder 27-28)
    - Cartoons, 1989-2000 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Casalini, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Cataloging, 2003-2008 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Cross Campus Library (CCL), 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Collection Development Committee (CDC) Digital Collection Task Force, 2006-2008 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC), 2004 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Council on Library and Information Resources (CLIR) Archiving, 1999-2008 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Council on Library and Information Resources (CLIR) Studies, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Conservation, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Consultant Reports, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Contracts, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Copyright, 1998-2009 (Box 1, Folder 40-43)
    - Copyright Handbook, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Copyright - University of Georgia, Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Cornell University Library, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Center for Research Libraries, 2003-2006 (Box 1, Folder 47-48)
    - Center for Research Libraries, 2007-2010 (Box 2, Folder 49-50)
    - Cervantes - Center for Research Libraries, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Collection Space Management Committee (CSM), 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 52-53)
    - Connecticut State - Textbook Summit, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Cyberinfrastructure, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Digital Advisory Working Group, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - DC Principles Coalition, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Development, 2006-2009 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Digital Landscape, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Digital Library Federation (DLF), 2000-2006 (Box 2, Folder 59a)
    - Digital Production and Integration Program (DPIP), 2006 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Digital Strategy, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Divinity School Annual Reports, 2004-2009 (Box 2, Folder 62-66)
    - E-BioMed, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - E-Books, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - E-Collections, 2002-2008 (Box 2, Folder 69-70)
    - eBrary, Undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - EBSCO, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - EEBO, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - ELI, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Electronic Reserves, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Elsevier, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 76-80)
    - Elsevier Scopus, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Endowment, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Equipment Requests, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - FEDORA, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Film, 2001-2008 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Finding Aids, Undated (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Floor Plan (AO), 2003 (Box 2, Folder 86a)
    - Fortunoff Video Archive, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Frye Institute, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Gale Agreements, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 90-91)
    - Gale Research - E-Mails, Notes, etc., 2005-2008 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - GLBTQ, 2004-2007 (Box 3, Folder 93-94)
    - Gay/Lesbian Studies Program, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Gehry Project, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Google, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Google Settlement, 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Harper's Weekly, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Harrassowitz, 2006-2008 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - High Wire Marketing Group, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Hill, Errol papers, 1982-2003 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - International Coalition of Library Consortia (ICOLC), 1995-2009 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - International Coalition of Library Consortia (ICOLC) - Presentations, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - International Centre for Theoretical Physics (ICTP), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Institute for the Future, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Institutional Repositories, 2003-2006 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Integrated Access Council, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Insurance - Yale Collections, 2002-2004 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - ISI Web of Science, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Ithaka Research Advisory Committee, 2005-2008 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Ivie's Plus, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Janus Conference, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Jointly Administered Knowledge Environment (JAKE), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Journal of Industrial Ecology (JIE), 2005 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - JSTOR, 2004-2010 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Kirtas - Library Executive Committee, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Large Scale Digitization, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 118a-118b)
    - Learned Publishing, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Letters, 1998-2009 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Liblicense, 2006-2008 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Library Journal, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Library of Congress (LC), 2007 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Library Shelving Facility (LSF), 2005-2008 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Library Systems Steering, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Licensing, 1996-2001 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Licensing - Digital Licensing Online Course, Undated (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Licensing UK Model License, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Licensing Workshops, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - LMC, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - LOCKSS Project, 2003-2006 (Box 4, Folder 131-132)
    - Manuscripts and Archives, 1996-2005 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - Maps, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Mass Deacidification, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Media, 2002-2007 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Media Task Force, Undated (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Medical Library, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Mellon Foundation, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Mellon Proposal - Social Sciences, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Mellon Proposal - UC Berkeley, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Miles Conrad Lecture, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Mudd Library Project, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Music Library, 1995-2008 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - National Academy of Sciences Conferences, 2004-2006 (Box 4, Folder 145-146)
    - National Library of Agriculture, Undated (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Nature, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Nelinet, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Northeast Research Libraries (NERL), 2008-2009 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Northeast Research Libraries (NERL) Annual Meeting, 2001-2006 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - New Haven Museum, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Newsletters - Misc, Undated (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Newspapers, 2001, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Newspapers Direct, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - National Institute of Health (NIH), 2008 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - North American Title, Undated (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - New York Art Resources Consortium (NYARC), 2006 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Online Computer Library Center (OCLC), 1999-2008 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Office of Digital Assets and Infrastructure (ODAI), 2008-2009 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - OhioLink, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Open Access, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Orphan Works, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Outsell - Info About Info, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Portico, 2005-2009 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Preservation, 2000-2007 (Box 4, Folder 166-172)
    - Preservation, 2008-2010 (Box 5, Folder 173-174)
    - ProQuest, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - ProQuest Offers, Projects, 1992-2004 (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - Research Libraries Group (RLG), 2006-2008 (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - Sakai, Undated (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - Scholarly Communications, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - Sponsoring Consortium for Open Access Publishing in Particle Physics (SCOAP3), 2008 (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - Security - Risk Evaluation, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - Stanford Encyclopedia of Philosophy (SEP), 2006 (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - Scholarly Publishing and Academic Resources Coalition (SPARC), 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - Social Sciences Library, 1999-2004 (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - Special Collections, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - Springer, 2004-2009 (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - Stanford, 1998-2008 (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - Scientific, Technial, and Medical (STM) Publishing, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - SQI, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 191)
    - Swets and Zeitlinger, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - T6 Grant Prep, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - Table of Contents Services, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - Tasini vs. NY Times, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 195)
    - TCP, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - Usage, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - Visiting Librarians, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - West Campus, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 200)
    - Wiley, 2003-2006 (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - Yale Office of Public Affairs, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - Yale Official, 1994-2008 (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - Yale University Press, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - Yankee Book Peddler, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 205)
  - Annual Reports
    - 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 205-207)
    - 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 208-209)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 210)
    - 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 211-213)
  - Collection Development
    - Acquisition Policies and Guidelines, 1954-1963 (Box 8, Folder 214-216)
    - Collecting Responsibilities, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 217-220)
  - Records of Michael Keller as associate university librarian for collection development
    - Chron Files, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 221)
    - Chron Files, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 222)
- Records of the US/UK Vendor Review Steering Committee, 2007; Accession 2013-A-048
  Restricted until January 1, 2042.
  - Committee notes and draft report, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Committee final report, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Blackwell's Book Services response to proposal, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - Coutts Information Services response to proposal, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - YBP response to proposal, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)